jscfcu.org 2010-06-15

# JSC FCU > About Us > Privacy Policy

**YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US  
**  
You provide important information about yourself to a variety of businesses and organizations. The same is true when you do business with our financial institution. You're asked to provide us with certain personal information that helps us give you better service and complete your transactions more effectively. 

We work diligently to safeguard the information you give to us. In fact, we developed the following policies to ensure you confidentiality and maintain your confidence in our institution. These policies detail the strict standards we have in place. For this reason we ask that you please read the following information carefully. 

**NOTICE OF YOUR FINANCIAL PRIVACY RIGHTS**

We, our, and us, when used in this notice, mean JSC Federal Credit Union. 

This is our privacy notice for our members. When we use the words "you" and "your" we mean the following types of members: 

Our consumer members who have a continuing relationship by purchasing or holding financial products or services such as a(n): 

  * Share account 
  * Loan account 
  * Credit card account 
  * Safe deposit box 

We will tell you the sources of the information we collect about you. We will tell you what measures we take to secure that information. 

We first define some terms.

Nonpublic personal information means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records. Hereafter, we will use the term "information" to mean nonpublic personal information as defined in this section. 

An affiliate is a company we own or control. 

A nonaffiliated third party is a person we do not employ or a company that is not an affiliate of ours. This is also known as nonaffiliated third party, or simply, an "other party."

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We collect information about you from the following sources: 

  * Information you give us on applications or other forms 
  * Information about your transactions with us 
  * Information about your transactions with other parties 
  * Information from a consumer reporting agency 
  * Information we receive through our Customer Identification Program 

**THE CONFIDENTIALITY, SECURITY, AND INTEGRITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We restrict access to information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect this information.   
**  
YOUR INFORMATION AND OTHER PARTIES**

We will not disclose information about you to anyone except as disclosed in this policy or as permitted by law. Examples of this might include disclosures necessary to service your account or prevent unauthorized transactions. 

**INFORMATION ABOUT FORMER MEMBERS**

We do not disclose information about former members, except as permitted by law. 

**AUTHORIZED SHARING - OUTSIDE MARKETING SERVICES**

We may disclose the following information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf: 

Information you give us on an application or other forms, such as: 

  * Name 
  * Address 

We disclose the information listed above with companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. You do not have a right to opt out of the disclosure of this information. We may also disclose information about you to other outside marketing services as permitted by law. 

Types of Businesses 

Here are the types of businesses with whom we may disclose information for outside marketing purposes: 

Service providers that perform marketing services for us, such as: 

  * Direct sales companies 
  * Reasons For Disclosing 

We may disclose information about you to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf to provide you with information about additional products and services. 

Limitations on Disclosure 

Here are the limitations we impose on the use of information disclosed to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf: 

  * We only allow direct mail solicitations. 
  * We do not allow telephone solicitations. 

**WEB SITE PRIVACY POLICY**

JSC Federal Credit Union is committed to protecting the privacy of its members and other users of its Web site. We limit the collection and storage of personal information to that necessary for us to administer our business, provide you with quality service and offer you opportunities we think might be of interest. We do not disclose any personal information collected from our Web site to unaffiliated organizations. 

When you visit any Web site, your â€œIP addressâ€ is recorded. We collect IP addresses for the sole purpose of tracking information to compile statistics to help us improve our site so that its users will find it more helpful and informative. The information is used solely for these analytical purposes and is discarded after use. This information is not distributed to third parties. 

We also use a technology called â€œcookiesâ€ to customize the site for returning visitors. A cookie is a small piece of data that is stored on a visitor's PC and later retrieved. This is used primarily in conjunction with STAR-PC so that we can enhance the level of security when you are using this service. Cookies might also be used to help you obtain information more quickly from certain sections of the Web site when returning. We use cookies for only these limited purposes. 

To provide you with greater access of information, JSC Federal Credit Union's site also contains links to other sites. While we hope these organizations join us in respecting your privacy, JSC FCU is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these other web sites. 

Finally, the above disclosure refers to information collected from you as you browse through or use our site to access information or conduct transactions. Information that you provide to us in an application for a service such as a loan, check order, new account or for a membership application is subject to the limitations imposed by our overall Privacy Policy which states that we will not disclose your nonpublic personal information to nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law. 

* * *

For more information on JSC Federal Credit Union, or to find out how you can join, please call 281.488.7070 or 800.940.0708, or visit any branch office or [e-mail](http://www.jscfcukb.org/contact.php).
